I'm Mao Ioki, a 465th Makizaka student, and today I came to Skiddy's to eat tuna!
I'm a bit of a line tuna lover, so I'm really into it today.
So here we go, Mai!
I've brought some preparations for you.
I was a narrator for a TV show called "My Road to School" and I received this at the end of the show and I love it so I thought I would bring it today.
I've brought it with me. There's a store I'm interested in, so I think I'll go there.
Let's go! Looks so good!
It looks too good!
The embodiment of happiness.
Delicious!
Let me tell you a piece of big news.
Actually...
I'm going to walk you right away.
I've already been to Tsukiji for an audition.
The day before the audition with my mom.
I remember saying to my mom the day before the audition that I wanted to go there because it was such a great opportunity.
I've always wanted to go there.
Today, I'm going to go to...
It's a restaurant called Tomboya where you can eat tuna steak.
I've never had tuna steak before.
I've never had tuna steak before, so I did a lot of research.
I've done a lot of research and came here because I wanted to go there!
Are we there yet?
Are we here?
Ta-da!
Dragonfly shop, right here.
There's a line.
Where's the best view?
I found the best view!
Oh, no!
Oh, this is so good!
Oh, it looks so good!
First time
I just ordered it.
Wow, it's grilled!
Is it medium fatty tuna? Is it medium fatty tuna?
Oh, my God! Fire!
Isn't this the best?
It's so cute.
I'm having so much fun.
Tasty morsels!
The store owner and the customers are chatting happily.
It's nice, isn't it?
I'm pretty near sick too.
like the shopping street I used to go to on my way home from school.
I like to make friends with the old ladies
That brings back memories.
She gave me croquettes and stuff like that.
She'd give it to me.
Like using a pesser.
Here's my little tuna steak.
Oh, here he comes!
We have a guest!
It's well done with garlic, so it's just as it is.
I understand.
Thank you.
You can leave it like that.
Yes, thank you very much.
Ta-da!
Oh, my God!
I'm so happy
Let's try it without anything at first.
Bon appétit!
Delicious!
I'll put a little pepper and lemon on it.
Yum!
It's so good!
Mmmmmmmm...
I remember now.
Here we go.
Here it comes!
My soy sauce
I'm going to use it.
Tamari soy sauce.
I haven't had a chance to eat sashimi lately.
I haven't been able to use it at all.
I'm going to use it.
It's so good!
You should try it too!
If you ever have a chance to come here on vacation, please do!
It's so good!
Finished it!
Delicious!
Finished!
It was so delicious. I'm so glad.
Well, I just finished eating the tuna steak,
I feel so happy,
Next time, I'd like to go eat something that's not tuna.Well, next time, I would like to go eat that specialty that is not tuna.
I eat it every time I come here,
I have a feeling there will be a long line today,
I love this street.
I like Rosiebla.
Rosie Uran.
Oh man, that looks delicious.
I can't get enough of it, because there are so many stores that I can't get through.
I want to conquer them all!
Flowers.
They're so cute!
So cute!
I like this town.
I like to find a place in Tokyo where I can feel the countryside.
I like to find a place where I can feel nature.
So if you have any recommendations, please let me know!
Oh! I can see it now.
Nah!
It's a crazy lineup!
Maybe it's a crazy lineup!
What's going on?
It's as crowded as a univa
Long line
The line is so long!
It's really bad!
I've been here already.
I've been wanting to go to Nogizaka since before I came to Nogizaka.
I've always wanted to go.
That hot griddle?
That frying pan.
And they cook a lot of eggs in that frying pan.
And then they cut them.
I used to admire that.
So I used a regular frying pan at home
I used a lot of eggs
I was trying to see how thin I could cut the omelet
I was trying to see how thin I could cut an omelet
But my mother was furious with me for using too many eggs.
Now that I live alone, I can do it again.
But now that I live alone, I don't do it anymore.
We don't even have an egg fryer at home.
An egg fryer?
Your face
It looks like you're going to fry a lot of eggs today.
I'm just...
I was really burning myself before I came in.
I was burning up before I went in.
During the final audition.
I had a meeting with the staff of Nogizaka.
I was told that if I wore sunscreen every day for six months, I would get whiter.
I thought they would say the same thing to me as everyone else.
What did they say? I was wondering if they would say the same thing to me as everyone else.
Did they tell you to wear sunscreen? No one said anything like that.
What? Only now?
That's because everyone is white.
I remember I was so embarrassed.
So I tried to do my best.
But I might have gotten into the habit of applying it every day.
That's good.
I'm getting close.
I'll show you.
It looks too good.
Well, I got it!
Oh, smells so good.
It smells so good!
Now I'd like to try some.
I'm going to eat it!
Bon appétit!
This is the taste!
Delicious!
It's a little sweet.
It's sweet, isn't it?
Warm.
What a price! 150 yen!
Delicious!
I don't know if I'm going to do it all today.
I'm doing it myself.
I wonder if a good sushi restaurant
Eggs.
It's like you can tell how good it tastes.
You can tell how good it tastes.
I've heard that.
That's why...
I don't always eat gross.
But I'll have an egg.
I'll just have one more bite.
It went fast.
Okay, well, I've already eaten.
I'll go on to the next one.I'll go next.
Well, it's a really nice day today.
I'm glad.
I'm surprised I haven't been to more places
There's so many places I've never been.
Crab.
I want some.
No, no, no... tuna today.
We're at the next restaurant.
There's a bit of a line.
We're at Siegen's.
Lines.
I'm in line at Segen's Seafood.
I'd like to talk to you about something.
I'd like to talk about some big news.
Big news? I don't know.
I'm going to tell you a story that's big news in my family.
I have relatives in Hyuugaizaka.
This is the first time I'm telling you this. I'm sure some of you may be wondering why I'm telling you this for the first time here.
I'm a cousin to this girl.
We've been doing New Year's, Christmas, birthday parties, etc. together since we were little.
We were very close.
When I moved to Tokyo, she threw me a party at the end of my stay.
What is her name?
Her name is Yoko Kogenji.
Yoco Kogenji, Yo-chan.
I used to call her Yopiko.
But when Yo-chan came here...
We're going to meet each other.
Actually, I came to Tsukiji.
The two of us together.
Yo-chan became Hinizaka.
That's how I ended up in Nogizaka.
My family is pretty normal.
We're all just a normal family.
But we've all been
It was a surprise for all of us.
You never know what life has in store for you.
So, I'm looking at you now, Yo-chan.
The 4th term student of Hinizaka
She's also the center of a new song
And she's doing a great job again.
It's really amazing.
She's been doing really well
In the past year
I've seen a lot of things change around me
Yochanan has changed, too.
I've told him that we're going to work hard together
I've been keeping it a secret from my fans
I've been keeping it a little secret from my fans.
Sometimes at story-telling sessions and such.
I've been asking her if she's interested in any of the 4th term students
I'd ask, "Is there anyone you're interested in? or something like that.
I'm from Hinomizaka prefecture, so I'd like fans from Hinomizaka to get to know her.
I hope you and Yo-chan will get along well.
I told him I'd like to talk to her.
I told him I'd like to talk to him.
Yesterday
It's like we met yesterday.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
That's what he said.
Surprised?
Oh, my God, this is it.
I think I can eat a little more.
Oh, no.
The view is amazing!
Char is doing it.
Delicious!
Here it comes! Thank you very much.
Now that it's here, I'd like to show you something.
Ta-da!
Oh, no!
This is bad.
Oh, no.
Oh, no!
Let's eat.
There's a spray.
I think I'll try spraying it on.
I don't know where to start.
Oh, no.
Oh, no. Oh, no.
Oh, shit. Oh, shit.
Oh, no.
This one...
A little bit of wasabi.
A little wasabi on top.
Bon appétit!
It's really delicious!Truly delicious!
I'll take your hand.
The most delicious at every sip!
Delicious!
Delicious
Truly delicious!
I don't know.
It makes me angry.
Delicious!
The embodiment of happiness.
The bijou is amazing!
What a bijou!
Is it possible to be this gorgeous?
Bon appétit!
I'm so lucky!
I've had the best tuna in Kaiten City for a long time.
I'm in Tobicue right now!
Tobicue the level!
I used to hate wasabi.
I feel like I've grown up.
Now I'm rather happy when I have it.
I put a little too much on.
A little bit
Spicy, but delicious!
What is this called?
Brilliance!
Oh my God, it's so shiny!
Oh my God!
I've got to show you...
I have to show them how good they look.
Twinkle, twinkle, twinkle.
I'll have the last piece.
It was delicious
I finished it
It was delicious I was happy
Thank you very much
I ate it.
It was outrageously delicious!
Yes, so today I came to eat tuna at Tsukinaka by myself!
I thought it was a great place to eat tuna and roe.
If you are ever in the area, please visit!
Thank you very much for your time today!
That's all for now.
Bye bye!
Please subscribe to our channel!
Please look forward to the next installment.